-Ny box and adjust the roof was the only error?
Well, then the moose spun around and slid off the roof.
And flew in the back of the car.
It knocked out both boxes at the back.
And destroyed the C-pillar.
-How did it go with you?
Not a scratch.
Not even glass splits.
-Why do you buy a car that has rolled 100,000 miles?
It's fun.
It had not rolled 100,000 miles when I bought it.
It had only rolled 94,000 miles when I bought it.
Here it falls out stuff.
It is almost all inspection protocols.
All receipts and everything done with the car.
In recent years it has been good and only been a small fix.
The last inspection did not go so well.
Rust in thresholds rear that is too close to bearing construction.
And bad lanterns.
A lamp that was loose, fog lights that were broken.
Handbrake that took bad and the springs that were off both sides.
-What do you have for future plans with this car?
I'll give it to a friend who has crashed with his car.
He drives more or less the earth.
He has done it the Senate 1.5 year.
So I sent the car in a container to the Netherlands.
When the car arrived we drove to Switzerland, Italy and Austria.
Oh my God!
Then I came up with the idea to put a large map on the bonnet.
So I can show everyone where the car has been.
I started by making a stretch from Japan to New Zealand.
Then a stretch to the Netherlands.
That's where my hobby started.
Last summer we drove to Northern Cape.
On to Russia which was almost 1000 miles.
And made that trip in 18 days.
Despite these trips, the car worked without any problems.
And drive from Miami to New York.
By then the car had also been to the United States.
The plan was to drive the car everywhere on the ground.
But two months ago ...
I drove on an icy road.
The car started to gossip and I drove too fast.
I drove into a tree at 80 km/h and everything broke on the car.
Even the crankshaft in the engine broke.
There was nothing to save on the car.
I felt bad because all the plans I had were now gone.
It was total chaos, I couldn't sleep or eat in a week.
There is something special about this car.
It has a wonderful story.
It will be fun to be able to travel in a car again.
The year 2020 will drive this car all the way from the Netherlands to Japan.
Drive the car back to the Subaru factory where it was manufactured.
I'm pretty sure we can drive all the way without any problems.
-It will cost a fortune?
Yes, but I hope I can find some sponsors.
That people can help pay for gasoline.
-What is the plan when you arrive at Japan.
Will you drive the car home?
If Subaru wants the car, they have to take it.
But if they do not want it, I will bring it home.
That's why I have jeans on me otherwise people look so strange at me.
-You seem to like the car.
Absolutely, I love it.
I have big plans.
I will foil large parts of the car.
All stories with the car, even small details like the scratches here at the back.
All scratches have their own history.
It should be foiled but the history of the car.
On the bonnet I will put a new map just like the old car.
Who will show the entire trip from the Netherlands to Japan.
Text about the plans for this car and that we drive a Subaru with 1 million km on the meter.
About the damage here when Viktor collided with a moose.
I came up with the name subglobe because I travel around the world in late Subaru.
That's why the website is called so.
On the Facebook page "Sunglobe - Team Legacy".
Can you follow all trips.
The goal is to drive to Japan.
And show the world ..
... that everyone has to buy a Subaru.
-It was very nice to meet and have a lovely trip home.
Thanks so much.
Bye!
There it goes.